얘들아, 이 구두 어때?
-Does everybody hate these shoes?
-Yeah.
별로긴 한데 타월만 두르고
있으면 아무도 신경 안 쓸 거야
But nobody will focus on that
if you wear that towel-dress.
말 좀 해줘
Tell him.
오늘 첫 출근하는 날인데
첫날부터 신경 긁으면 안되지
It's her first day at this new job.
You shouldn't start with her.
알았어, 하루만 기다리지 뭐
All right.
I suppose I can wait a day.
-What are you doing Friday?
-Why?
- 금요일에 뭐해?
- 왜?
Come to my weird cousin Albert's
bachelor party.
괴짜 사촌 앨버트가
총각파티에 오라고 해서
식물학자 알지?
You know, he's the botanist?
그럼, 식물학자들은 죄다
괴짜라니까
Oh, God!
Botanists are such geeks.
맞아
Is that a dinosaur tie?
- 그거 공룡 넥타이야?
- 응
- 안녕
Morning!
Rach, I'm here with the purses!
레이첼, 가방 가져왔어
열쇠 찾으려면 종일 걸리겠다
It must take you forever
to find your keys.
고마워, 정말 고마워
Thank you, Pheebs.
거북이 가방 들고 갈래?
You're welcome. Please want the one
with the turtles.
아니, 난 거북이 무서워
오늘은 안 할래
No, turtles scare me.
I don't need that today.
걱정하지 마, 괜찮을 거야
Honey, just relax.
It's gonna be fine.
내가 가서 점심 사줄까?
Why don't I come
and take you to lunch?
고맙지만 괜찮아
마크랑 같이 먹을 거야
Thank you!
But Mark's taking me out.
마크? 자기 취직하는 거
도와준 그 마크?
Mark? Is that the same Mark
that helped you get the job?
응, 첫날이라 행운을
빈다는 의미에서...
It's like a "good luck on your
first day" thing.
Is this a lunch box?
이거 진짜 도시락이야?
아니, 가방이야
근데 보온도 되는 거야
No, a purse.
And there's a thermos in it.
-So can you make it on Friday?
-What?
금요일에 시간 되겠어?
그럴 것 같긴 한데
왜 날 또 초대한 거야?
I think so.
Why am I invited to this again?
앨버트가 친구가 없거든
Apparently, Albert has no friends.
He's excited about the bachelor party.
총각 파티에 잔뜩 기대를
걸고 있어
잘은 몰라도 스트리퍼 보려고
결혼하는 걸 거야
He's only getting married
so he can see a stripper.
A stripper at a bachelor party.
That is so cliche.
총각 파티에 스트리퍼라니,
너무 진부하다
Why don't you guys get a magician?
마술사를 부르지 그래?
If he can open my beer
with his butt-cheeks, then all right.
마술사가 엉덩이로 맥주병
따주면, 그것도 좋겠지
The One With All the Jealousy
그 남자랑 점심을 한대
점심을!
She's having lunch with him?
Lunch with him?
취직됐다는 말 들었을 때
그 남자한테 안기더라구
You should've seen him hug her
when she got the job!
그 친구 정말 잘생겼단 말야
And he's really good-looking.
어떻게 하지?
-What am I gonna do?
-You don't do anything.
아무 것도 하지 마
마음 속에 담아둬
감정 숨기는 법을 배워야지
IKeep it inside.
Learn how to hide your feelings.
Don't cry out loud.
징징 짜지도 말고
됐어!
Guess who has an audition
for a Broadway musical?
누가 브로드웨이 뮤지컬
오디션 받게?
I wanna say you, but it seems like
such an easy answer.
너라고 말하고 싶지만
너무 쉬운 답이 아닐까?
It is me!
나야! '두 도시 이야기'의
뮤지컬 버전이래
It's a musical version
of A Tale of Two Cities.
So I think I'm gonna sing
"New York, New York"...
그래서 '뉴욕 뉴욕'이나
'샌프란시스코에 내 마음을
두고 왔어요'를 부를까 해
...and "I Left My Heart
in San Francisco."
조이, 도시를 네 맘대로
고를 수 있을까?
Joey, I don't think
you get to pick the cities.
What?
뭐?
Mr. Dickens gets to pick them.
위에서 골라주겠지
Who?
누구?
I'll get you the Cliff Notes.
'모집 요강' 갖다줄게
The what?
뭐?
요약본
The abridgment.
아, 그거...
The what?
뭐라고?
패션 스타일 번호
Then the style number...
송장 번호
...the invoice number
and the shipping date.
선적 날짜
Good. Any questions so far?
좋아요
지금까지 질문 있어요?
네, 직원 디스카운트는
몇 프로예요?
What kind of discount do we get?
Twenty percent.
20%요
너무 좋아요
I love this job!
첫 번째 전화네
-My first call!
-Here, let me.
내가 받을게요
Rachel Greene's line.
May I help you?
레이첼 그린 전용선입니다
뭘 도와드릴까요?
Hi, is Rachel there?
레이첼 있어요?
누구시라고 전해드릴까요?
-And who may I say is calling?
-This is Ross.
로스인데요
- 로스 누구...
- '로스와 레이첼'의 로스요
Ross of...?
Of "Ross and Rachel."
안녕하세요, 마크예요
Hi, it's Mark.
안녕하세요, 마크
-Hey, Mark.
-Hey.
- 안녕
- 네
Hold on a second.
It's Ross.
- 잠깐만요
- 그래요
로스예요
Hi, honey.
안녕, 자기야
안녕, 근데 왜 마크가
자기 전화를 받아?
What's Mark doing
answering your phone?
놀러 왔어
Oh, he's just goofing around.
진짜 웃기네
Oh, that's funny.
자기 사무실에서 놀면 되잖아
Why isn't he goofing around
in his own office?
This is his office too. I told you,
we're Joanna's two assistants.
이 사람 사무실도 된다니까
우린 둘 다 조아나의 조수야
Why does Joanna need two assistants?
조아나는 왜 조수가 둘이나
필요해? 얼마나 게으르면!
How lazy is she?
- 맙소사, 어쩜 좋아
- 왜?
Oh, my God! What did I just do?
I just shipped 3000 bras to Personnel!
브래지어 3천 개를 인사과로
보내버렸어, 끊어야겠어
I gotta go!
Mark, I need you!
마크, 도와줘요
Okay! Bye-bye!
알았어, 안녕
로스
미안해, 다른 번호를
누른다는 게 그만...
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I was just trying to
I was dialing another number.
I got changed in 30 seconds
so you could be alone with him.
좋아, 단둘이 있으라고
자리 비켜줄거니까
You better go for it.
대쉬해봐
I'm not going for anything.
내가 왜 대쉬를 해?
네가 안 하면 내가 한다
Well, if you don't, I will.
Would you please go?
그만 가줄래?
'Night, Mon.
안녕, 모니카
'Night, Julio.
- 안녕, 훌리오
- 아디오스
누가 책을 두고 갔나봐요
Someone left their book here.
Actually, that is mine.
내 거예요
그래요?
What are you reading?
뭔데요?
Flowers of Evil, by Baudelaire.
Have you read it?
보들레르의 '악의 꽃'이에요
읽었어요?
Have I read it?
읽었냐구요?
No. Are you enjoying it?
아뇨, 재밌어요?
그런 대로요
근데 번역이 형편없어요
I thought I would,
but the translation's no good.
You're a poet
and you don't know it.
시인도 아니면서
뭘 안다구요
Actually, l....
난 사실... 시인이에요
I am a poet.
So you do know it.
그럼 얘기가 다르죠
뭐에 대해 쓰는데요?
So what kind of things
do you write about?
날 감동시키는 거요
나무의 그림자...
Things that move me:
The shadow of a tree...
...a child laughing...
아이들의 웃음...
...or this lip.
아름다운 입술...
Mine?
입술? 이거요?
Right here?
이 입술에 대해서라면
서사시도 쓸 수 있어요
I could write an epic poem
about this lip.
How would that go?
어떻게요?
Well, it didn't rhyme...
운은 안 맞지만...
...but I liked it.
맘에 들어요
You've got to pick a pocket or two...
주머니 한 두 개를 털어요
...boys
You've got to pick a pocket...
주머니 한 두 개를 털어야죠
... or two
Lovely.
좋아요,
아주 좋아요
Just lovely.
정말요? 고마워요
Really? Thanks.
We definitely want to see you
for the callback on Saturday.
토요일에 꼭 다시
봤으면 좋겠어요
좋아요
Excellent!
갈게요
I'll be there.
댄스 오디션 볼 때
재즈 슈즈 꼭 가져와요
Don't forget to bring your jazz shoes
for the dance audition.
댄스 부문이 아니라고
들었는데요
My agent said that
it wasn't a dancing part.
다들 춤은 조금씩 춰야 돼요
All the roles gotta dance a little.
But with your dance background,
it'll be a piece of cake.
조이의 댄스 실력 정도면
걱정없어요
틸라 타프와 현대 무용 3년
"Three years of modern dance
with Twyla Tharp"?
"Five years with
the American Ballet Theatre"?
아메리칸 발레
씨어터에서 5년?
이력서에 다 거짓말 쓰잖아
Everybody lies on their resume, okay?
I wasn't one of
the Zoom kids either.
나만 손해볼 순 없지
Well, can you, like, dance at all?
너 춤 출 줄이나 알아?
그럼, 알잖아
Yeah, I can dance.
You know....
안돼, 안돼, 안돼!
What is that?
그게 뭐야?
물론 어설퍼 보일 거야
음악이 없으니까
Sure, it looks stupid now.
There's no music playing.
I have to get that.
But, no, no.
내가 받을게, 제발 하지 마!
여보세요
Hi.
안녕하세요
네
Listen, I'm in need of a stripper
and I was told that you do that.
스트리퍼가 필요한데,
해주시겠다구요?
Let me ask you this. What do you do
for the extra hundred?
하나만 물어볼게요
추가 백달러는 왜 필요하죠?
So would I have to provide the grapes?
그럼 제가 포도를
준비해야 되는 건가요?
Hi.
안녕
어제 훌리오랑은 어땠어?
How was last night
with Julio, senorita?
It was amazing. He's sexy and smart,
which makes him even sexier.
아주 좋았어
정말 섹시하고
똑똑한 사람이야
그래서 더 섹시하게 느껴져
그리고 있잖아
Last night we were fooling around...
어제 한참 즐기는데 갑자기
시를 쓴다며 멈추는 거야
...and all of a sudden he stops
to write a poem.
Get out! I couldn't stop
if a meteor hit me.
말도 안돼, 난 바위가
굴러와도 못 멈추겠다
좋아, 스트리퍼를 구했어
'미스 크리스탈 챈들리에'
We have our stripper,
a "Miss Crystal Chandelier."
Name a kid that, what do you
expect them to grow up to be?
네 딸 이름 그렇게 지어라
커서 뭐가 될까 걱정된다
집에 가면서 깜빡 잊고
시를 놓고 갔지 뭐야
But he forgot
to take the poem with him.
난 시를 모르지만
꽤 괜찮은 것 같아, 볼래?
I am totally dense about poetry,
but I think this is pretty good.
Check it out.
"The Empty Vase.
Translucent beauty"
- '빈 병', 투명한 아름다움
- 속으로 좀 읽어라
To yourself.
You know, that's pretty good.
정말 굉장한데
- 그렇지?
- 그래
Yeah, I think so too.
Phoebe?
- 피비 너는?
- 좋다
너희가 좋다니까 나도 좋다
일하러 가야 돼
Great!
I'm so glad you guys like it!
-I gotta go to work.
-I'm not done.
아직 안 끝났어
Give it back when
you're through.
좋아, 나중에 돌려줘
나중에 보자
-See you guys.
-Bye-bye.
- 잘 가
- 안녕
어떡해, 큰일이야
가엾은 모니카
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Poor Monica!
What? What? What?
왜, 왜?
이 시를 썼을 때
모니카하고 있었다면서?
He was with her
when he wrote this poem!
이거 봐, '아무 것도 담고 있지
않은 사랑스러운 나의 빈 병'
"My vessel so lovely,
with nothing inside"?
'그대를 만지니 더더욱
텅 빈 공간이 느껴지네'
"Now that I've touched you,
you seem emptier still"?
모니카가 비었다고 보는 거야
모니카가 빈 병이라구
He thinks Monica's empty.
She's the empty vase!
You really think he meant that?
- 정말 그런 뜻일까?
- 그렇다니까
Totally.
모니카는 아무 것도 모르고
좋아하잖아
Oh, God!
And she seems so happy too.
Done.
다 읽었다
Do you have the Ralph Lauren file?
랄프 로렌 파일 있어요?
Oh, yeah, sure! It's right
그럼요, 네...
이게 뭐예요?
What's that?
로스가 보낸 거예요
'사랑의 딱정벌레'요
It's from Ross. It's a Love Bug.
남자친구가 있다는 걸
알리고 싶은가 보죠?
Somebody wants people to know
you have a boyfriend.
아뇨, 그런 게 아니에요
워낙 로맨틱한 사람이거든요
That's not what he's doing.
He's just really romantic.
- 레이첼 그린 양이십니까?
- 네
Excuse me. Are you Rachel Greene?
One, two, three.
하나, 둘, 셋
Congratulations on your first week
At your brand-new job
새 직장에서의 첫 날을
축하해요
It won't be long
Before you're the boss
곧 승진도 할 거예요
And you know who will be there
To support you
늘 당신 곁에 있어줄 사람은
누구일까요?
Your one and only boyfriend
- 하나 뿐인 남자친구랍니다
- 남자친구가 있으면 좋죠
It's nice to have a boyfriend!
Your loyal, loving boyfriend, Ross!
당신만을 사랑하는 남자친구
로스, 로스!
I'm hurt!
I'm actually hurt...
나 상처 받았어
상처 받았다구
...that you'd think I'd send those
things out of anything but love.
사랑이 아닌 다른 이유로 '사랑의
메신저'를 보냈다고 생각하다니
Hurt!
상처야, 상처 받았다구
All right, I get it. You're hurt!
- 알았어, 알아들었어
- 정말 너무하잖아
여자친구한테 '사랑의 메신저'도
맘대로 못 보내는 거야?
Can't a guy send
a barbershop quartet...
...to his girlfriend's office anymore?
Oh, please!
It was so obvious...
속 보이는 짓 그만해, 지금
자기는 영역을 표시하는 거잖아
...Iike you were marking
your territory.
내 사무실에 와서 사방에
쉬를 하고 다니는 꼴이라구
You might as well have just come in
and peed around my desk!
I would never do that.
사람을 뭘로 보는 거야?
Look, I know what's going on here.
무슨 생각하는지 다 알아
마크가 다 얘기해줬어
Mark explained it all to me.
He said this is what you guys do.
남자들이 원래 다 그렇대
마크가 그런 말을 했다면
마크는 바보야
Well, if Mark said that,
then Mark's an idiot.
천재네
Mark's a genius.
Why? How?
How is he a genius?
어떻게 마크가 천재야?
Don't you see what's happening?
어떻게 돌아가는지 모르겠어?
Instead of hitting on her now,
he's becoming her confidante.
단방에 채가는 대신 차츰
신뢰를 얻어가고 있는 거야
Now he's gonna be the guy she goes to,
to complain about you.
결국엔 레이첼이 그 친구한테
네 불평을 늘어놓게 될걸
어떡하면 좋지?
What am I gonna do?
'사랑의 딱정벌레'라도
보내지 그래?
Why don't you send her a musical bug?
No, you already did that.
참, 벌써 보냈지
좋아, 이번엔 직접 찾아가봐
You're gonna have to go
there yourself now.
깜짝 방문을 하는 거지
Make a few surprise visits.
모르겠어
I don't know, guys.
Fine, don't do anything.
Sit and talk to us.
네가 여기서 뭉개고
있는 동안
Meanwhile, she is talking
to him about you.
레이첼은 마크하고
너에 대해 얘기하고 있어
그 친구는 귀기울여
듣고 있지
And he's being Mr. Joe Sensitive.
She's thinking, "Maybe he's the guy
for me because he understands me."
레이첼은 자신을 잘 이해해주는
마크에게 점점 빠져드는 거야
어느새 레이첼은
마크한테 가버리고
And before you know it,
she's with him.
And you'll be all, "Oh, man!"
그럼 넌 이러겠지, '어떡해! '
And he'll be all, "Yes!"
그 친구는 이러겠지, '좋았어! '
And us, we'll be like, "Oh, dude!"
그럼 우린 이럴 거야
'안됐다, 친구! '
그럼 넌 또 이러겠지
'안녕'
And pretty soon you'll be like:
"Hi."
'난 안 갈래, 레이첼이랑
마크도 올 테니까'
And, "Well, I can't go.
Rachel and Mark might be there."
그럼 우린 이러겠지
'그만해, 벌써 4년이나 됐잖아'
And we'll be like, "Man, get over it!
It's been four years!"
He paints quite a picture,
doesn't he?
너무 생생하지 않냐?
12월 목록 가져왔어요
Here's the Shelley Segal stuff
for December.
Wait, I've got something for you.
잠깐, 선물이 있어
- 마크
- 괜찮아, 레이첼도 알아
It's okay. Rachel knows.
그래도...
Yeah, but even so
못 참겠어
당신 때문에 미치겠다구
I can't help it.
I'm just crazy about you.
너무 낭만적이다
Oh, that is so sweet!
나답지 않다는 거 알아
I know I'm Mr. Inappropriate today,
but it's just so tough.
너무 힘들어서 그래
당신을 만지고 안고 싶어
I see you walking around,
and I want to touch and hold you....
Come on, no one's around.
Just kiss me.
이리 와, 아무도 없잖아
키스해줘
그만해, 저리 떨어져
저리 떨어지란 말야!
All right, that's it!
Get off of her!
What is going on?
무슨 일이죠?
무슨 일이냐고?
지금 그런 말이 나와?
What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on!
로스?
넥타이 하나 사려고
20분이나 기다리고 있었어요
I have been down in your store
for 20 minutes, trying to get a tie.
도대체 서비스가 왜
이 모양이죠?
What do I have to do
to get some service?
Hi, Rach.
안녕, 레이첼
조이?
조이 트리비아니?
Joey Tribbiani?
문제가 생겼어요
I've got a problem.
I just got a call
from my dance captain.
무용 감독이 전화했는데
He's having a relationship crisis
and can't leave Long lsland.
문제가 생겨서 롱 아일랜드를
나올 수 없대요
그럼 오디션은 취소예요?
Does that mean the audition's off?
Seeing as you've got
the most experience...
조이가 경력이 제일 많으니까
... I want you to teach these dancers
the combination.
무용수들한테 안무를 짜서
가르쳐주면 좋겠어요
What?
뭐라구요?
어려울 거 없잖아요
Come on, it's easy.
You know, it's hand, hand...
이런 식으로, 손, 손, 머리,
머리, 올리고, 파드브리, 돌고
... head, head...
... up, pas de bourree,
pas de bourree...
... big turn here, rond de jambe....
한 바퀴 돌고, 다시 돌고,
옆으로, 스텝, 스텝, 손 흔들고!
Slide, step, step...
...and jazz hands!
So that's, "Steppity-step
and jazz hands."
스텝 밟고 손 흔들고요?
Have fun.
부탁해요
Bye.
안녕
- 안녕
뭐야?
What are you wrapping?
Look what I got Julio.
훌리오 주려고
It's a vase.
꽃병이네
시에 나온 거랑 같은 거야
Just like the one in the poem.
시에 나온 거랑 똑같진 않다
Not exactly like
the one in the poem.
What do you mean?
무슨 소리야?
너 시에 대해선 아무 것도
모른다고 했지?
Remember how you said you were
really dense about poetry?
응
So I'm just an empty vase?
- 내가 빈 병이라구요?
- 네?
What?
당신만큼 중요한 책을
많이 안 읽은 건 사실이에요
So, I don't read as many
important books as you do.
And I don't write trick poems
that aren't about what they seem.
어떤 한 가지에 대해 어려운
시를 쓰는 것도 아니구요
And I get excited about
stupid stuff...
그리고 말예요, 난 아무 것도
아닌 일에 흥분해요
주말에 '수근수근 잡지'가
오거나
...Iike when my
People magazine comes...
'전품목 카탈로그'가
오면 미치죠
...and the new
"Hold Everything" catalog.
But that doesn't mean I'm empty. I
care about things. Friends and family.
그렇다고 내가 텅 빈 건
아니에요
난 늘 가족과 친구들을
생각하죠
당신이 무슨 권리로
그런 판단을 내리는 거죠?
You have no right to judge me!
You don't even know me!
날 알지도 못하잖아요
The poem is not about you.
그 시는 당신에 대해
쓴 게 아니에요
What?
네?
'빈 꽃병'은 당신이 아니에요
"The Empty Vase" is not about you.
My baby preciosa....
내 사랑...
You make me so sad
that you would think this.
그렇게 생각하면
내가 슬퍼져요
미안해요,
내 친구 피비가...
I'm sorry. It's....
My friend Phoebe said
그건 모든 여자들에
대한 시예요
It's about all women.
Well...
...all American women.
모든 미국 여성에 대한 거죠
You feel better now?
- 기분이 좀 나아졌어요?
- 아무렴요
All right, let's do it.
좋아요, 시작합시다
아니, 아니...
이게 뭐죠?
What was that?
It's the best
I could get out of them.
그러게요
아무리 해도 안되네요
Well, people!
여러분
People, people, people!
여러분, 여러분...
Let's try it again. And this time,
everybody watch Joey.
다시 한번 해봅시다
이번엔 조이를 잘 봐요
Show 'em how it's done.
시범을 보여줘요
Count it off, Mack.
시작해요, 맥
Did you have fun at
the bachelor party last night?
어젯밤 총각파티는
재미있었어?
그럼, 이것 좀 볼래?
Look what I got!
See, she's dressed, right?
- 지금은 옷 입었지?
- 응
And then you click it,
and uh-oh, she's naked!
이걸 누르면
홀라당이네
And then you click it again
and she's dressed.
다시 누르면
옷을 입고 있지
직장 여성이야
She's a business woman
walking down the street.
길을 걸으면서 아이쇼핑을
하고 있는데 갑자기....
She's window shopping,
and oh, she's naked!
옷이 홀라당!
안녕
어서와
I'm gonna spend some alone time
with the pen.
난 이 펜이랑 둘만의 시간을
가져야겠다
바보처럼 굴어서 미안해
I'm sorry. I was an idiot.
A big idiot.
- 못말리는 바보였지
- 못말리는 바보였어
A big idiot.
It's just,
you have to realize...
자기가 이해해줘
마크 일은 너무 힘들었어
...this Mark thing is hard for me.
뭐가 힘들어?
우리 사귄 지 벌써 1년째잖아
Why is it hard? We've been together
for almost a year now.
Well, I was with Carol
for, like, eight years.
캐롤하고는 8년이나 됐는데
헤어졌어
And I lost her.
And now, if it's possible,
I think I love you even more.
지금은 자기를 내가 너무
많이 사랑하잖아
그래서 생각만 해도 힘들어
So it's hard for me
to believe I'm not gonna...
...well, that someone else isn't
gonna take you away.
누가 자기를 뺏어가
버릴까 겁이 나
그게 나였으면...
나였으면...
Let it be me. Let it be me!
Honey, that's very sweet.
자기 맘 이해하지만
It just seems to me, though,
that if two people love each other...
두 사람이 서로 사랑한다면
서로를 믿어야지
...and trust each other,
like we do...
우리처럼...
질투할 이유가 없잖아
...there's no reason to be jealous.
가야겠다
간다, 챈들러
I gotta get going.
Bye, Chandler.
그래, 펜이 지루한 모양인데
포르노 테잎 하나 빌려올래?
This pen's getting kind of boring.
Can you pick me up some porn?
Where you going?
어디 가는데?
벤 데리러 가야 돼
오후에 갈 데가 있거든
I've gotta go pick up Ben
for a play-date this afternoon.
With who?
누구랑?
어제 파티에서 만났던 여자랑
Just this woman I met last night
at the party.
여자라면...
There was a woman at?
The stripper?
스트리퍼?
그래
You have a play-date with a stripper?
스트리퍼를 만나기로 했어?
Man, I gotta get a kid!
나도 애 하나 낳아야지
일 끝낸 다음에
그 여자랑 얘기를 해봤는데
We started talking
after she did her thing...
...and she's got a boy
about Ben's age.
벤 나이 또래 만한 아들이
하나 있더라구
보이스카웃 교실에 같이
가기로 했어
So we're gonna take the kids
to a Gymboree class.
-ls that okay?
-Sure. Is she married?
괜찮지?
- 그럼, 유부녀 맞지?
- 아니
Are you jealous?
질투하는 거야?
아니, 난 그냥 왜 그 여자가
자길 만나는지 이해가 안 가서...
I just don't see why she has
to play with you.
I mean, doesn't she have any other
stripper-mom friends of her own?
그 여자는 스트리퍼
엄마 친구들도 없대?
You are totally jealous!
질투하는 거야
I'm not jealous.
질투하는 거 아냐, 그냥...
This is about...
사람들이 스트리퍼에 대해 갖는
일반적인 감정에 대해...
... people feeling certain things...
...you know, about...
...strippers. And, you know....
말하는 것 뿐이야
- 그리고 말야...
- 나도 사랑해, 자기야
I love you too.
Bye.
안녕
Wait, wait, wait!
- 잠깐, 잠깐...
- 왜?
What?
Well, there's a kiss he won't forget
for a few hours.
키스해줬으니까 한동안은
잊지 못하겠지?
Either that or you just turned him on
and sent him to a stripper.
스트리퍼한테 가는데
너무 흥분시켰다
Is there a Julio here?
훌리오 있어요?
I am Julio.
전데요
Mr. Pretentious
허풍쟁이 아저씨
잘난 척 그만 하시죠
You think there's no one finer
Your poems are unpublished
시집을 낸 것도 아니고
식당에서 일하는 주제에
And you work in a diner
여자들을 꽉 쥐고 있다고
생각한다면 그건 착각이죠
You're no God's gift to women
That's all in your head
You are just a butt-munch
- 아저씨는 허풍쟁이
- 허풍쟁이는 재수없어
No one likes a butt-munch!
And you're also bad in bed
침대에서도 꽝이잖아